Guide to the Office of the President records, 1795-2007 RG0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Lloyd H. Elliott records, 1927-1989; 1965-1988; Series 4; 62.5 Linear Feet 39 record center cartons, 8 document boxes
  - University oganization files, 1953-1974; 1958-1972; Series 4 Sub-series 4; 13.5 Linear Feet 9 record center cartons
    This sub-series is a set of "University organization" files, which are files of correspondence and other materials organized by the university unit to which they relate. University organization files are differentiated from the alphabetical correspondence files in that they pertain exclusively to correspondents and subejcts internal to the university.
    Although these files date primarily from the Elliott presidency, they include some materials from the administrations of his predecessors, Colclough and Carroll. These files were retired from active use around 1974.
    The subjects include Commission on Governance, Faculty Assembly, commencements and convocations, athletics such as football, Admissions Office, Computer Center, College of General Studies, Law Center, groundbreaking of the law library and the Patent and Trademark Institute, registrar records, sponsored research, medical affairs, Medical Center, Black Students Union, Marvin Center, fund-raising campaigns, student protests and demonstrations, Faculty Senate, Smith Center, and University Historian. There are many files for various committees such as University Bookstore Committee, Student Publications Committee, and Academic Policy Committee. Of particular note are the University Marshall files, which include programs that list graduates from various commencements.
    - President's Office: President Colclough's Report on University, 01/22/1960 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - President's Office: Annual Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - President's Office: All University Assembly - Agenda and Minutes, 1972-1973; 2 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 4, Folder 5)
    - President's Office: All University Senate Proposal - Replies from Faculy, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - President's Office: All -University Senate Proposal - Replies from Non-Academic Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - President's Office: All University Senate Proposal - Replies from Student, undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - President's Office: Organizations and Students, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - President's Office: Commission on Governance- Actions of Board of Trustees, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - President's Office: Relating to Governance of University (Weitzel), 1968 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - President's Office: Commission on Governance, 1969-1973; 2 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 12, Folder 13)
    - President's Office: Consultant to the President (Farrington), 1969-1972 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - President's Office: Special Assistant to the President (Farrington) - Heads of State Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - President's Office: Dean in the President's Office (Dreese), 1959-1961 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - President's Office: Faculty Assembly Minutes, 1960-1972; 3 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 19)
    - President's Office: Faculty Assembly Special Committee of Inquiry - Selection of President, 1964-1965; 2 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 20, Folder 21)
    - President's Office: Faculty Assembly - Faculty Organization Plan, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Marshal of the University: General, 1953-1965 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Marshal of the University: Degrees-Conferred, 09/30/1972 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Marshal of the University: Commencement - National Law Center, 06/04/1972 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Marshal of the University: Commencement - Medical School, 05/28/1972 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Marshal of the University: Commencements, 05/14/1972 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Marshal of the University: Convocation, 02/21/1972 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Marshal of the University: Degrees Conferred (Not in Box), 09/30/1971 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Marshal of the University: Commencements, 06/1971 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Marshal of the University: Commencement - Medical School, 05/1971 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Marshal of the University: Commencement Program, 05/1971-06/1971 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Marshal of the University: Sesquicentennial Convocation, 02/15/1971 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Athletics: General, 1966-1972 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Athletics: Football, 1965-1967 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Athletics: National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Athletics: Southern Conference, 1966-1970 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Budget Director: General, 1966-1972; 3 folder(s) (Box 61, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Degrees Conferred, 09/30/1970 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencements, 05/1970-06/1970 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement Programs, 05/1970-06/1970 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/21/1970 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Degrees Conferred, 09/30/1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/08/1969 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1969 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Degrees Conferred, 09/30/1968 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/02/1968 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1968 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Degrees Conferred, 09/30/1967 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/04/1967 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1967 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Degrees Conferred, 09/30/1966 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/05/1966 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/21/1966 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/06/1965 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1965 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/07/1964 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1964 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/05/1963 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/21/1963 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/06/1962 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1962 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 10/21/1961 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/07/1961 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1961 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 10/22/1960 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/01/1960 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 08/31/1960 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/22/1960 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 10/17/1959 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/03/1959 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/03/1959 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 02/23/1959 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Convocation, 10/18/1958 (Box 62, Folder 36)
    - President's Office Marshall of the University: Commencement, 06/04/1958 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    - Academic Affairs: General - (Provost), undated (Box 62, Folder 38)
    - Academic Affairs: Deans Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 39)
    - Academic Affairs: Dean of Faculties and Vice President, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 40)
    - Academic Affairs: Academic Editor, undated (Box 62, Folder 41)
    - Admissions Office: General, 1966-1972 (Box 62, Folder 42)
    - Admissions Office: Art Curator's Report (Dr. Teller), 1968 (Box 62, Folder 43)
    - Columbian College: General, 1958-1972 (Box 62, Folder 44)
    - Columbian College: Departments, 1959-1970; 2 folder(s) (Box 62, Folder 45, Folder 46)
    - Columbian College: Finian Report, 12/05/1965 (Box 62, Folder 47)
    - Columbian College: Honors Program, 1966-1969 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Columbian College: Junior College, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Columbian College: Minutes, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Columbian College: Physics Department, Departmental Science Development, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Columbian College: Proposal to National Science Foundation, 06/15/1967 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Computer Center: General, 1965-1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Degree Changes: General, 1958-1967 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Education, School of: General, 1962-1972 (Box 63, Folder 8, Folder 9)
    - Education, School of: Selection of Dean, 1966-1968 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Education, School of: Elementary Teacher Education, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Education, School of: ERIC, 1968-1972 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Education, School of: Home Economics, 1958-1961 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Education, School of: Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Education, School of: National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1964-1969 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Education, School of: Washington School of Psychiatry, 1964-1969 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Education, School of: Wise Program, 1966-1968 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of: General, 1958-1972; 3 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 18, Folder 19, Folder 20)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of: Dean, Selection of, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of: Center for Measurement Science, 1960-1968 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of: Engineers Council for Professional Development, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of: Institute for Management Science and Engineering, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Engineering & Applied Science, School of: Minutes, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Federal Programs, Developing Colleges: General, 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - General Studies, College of: General, 1960-1972; 2 folder(s) (Box 63, Folder 27, Folder 28)
    - General Studies, College of: Dover Air Force Base, Delaware, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - General Studies, College of: Naval War College, Newport, R.I., 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - General Studies, College of: Tidewater Area, 1964-1966 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Government & Business Administration, School of: General, 1966-1972 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Government & Business Administration, School of: Selection of Dean, 1971-1973 (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Government & Business Administration, School of: Fellowship Programs, 1956-1971 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Government & Business Administration, School of: Health Care Administration Program, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Government & Business Administration, School of: Minutes, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: General(School Closed Out), 1966 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: General, 1959-1965 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: Behavioral Sciences Center, 1962-1966 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: Dooley Report, 06/1962 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: Reorganization, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: Scottish Rite Supreme Council, 1961-1966 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: Sino Soviet Studies Program, 1961-1965 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Gov., Business & International Affairs, School of: Tregaron, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: General, 1966-1972 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: General (Former Graduate Council), 1962-1966 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Fellowship, 1967-1972 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Minutes, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Natural Resources Policy Center, 1967-1969 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Graduate School of Arts & Sciences: Natural Resources Policy Studies, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Consortium: General, 01/1973-06/1973 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Consortium: General, 01/1972-12/1972 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Consortium: General, 1970-1971 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Consortium: General, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Consortium: General, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Consortium: General, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Consortium: Chief Executive Officer Candidates, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Consortium: Proposed International Education Center, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Consortium: Science & Technology Center, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Consortium: Washington Consortium - Articles of Incorporation, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Consortium: Washington Consortium - General, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Law Center: General, 1970-1972 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Law Center: General, 1966-1969 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Law Center: General, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Law Center: Dulles Fund for International Legal Studies, 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Law Center: Graduate School of Public Law, 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Law Center: Graduate School of Public Law, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Law Center: Law Library Dedication & Luncheon, 02/22/1969 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Law Center: Law School, General, 1959-1965 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Law Center: Law School, Forensic Medicine Institute, 1959-1960 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Law Center: Law School - Special Convocation 100th Anniversary, undated (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Law Center: Groundbreaking - Law Library, 10/12/1965 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Law Center: Law, Psychiatry & Criminology Institute, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Law Center: Law Center Minutes, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Law Center: Patent, Trademark & Copyright Research Inst., 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Law Center: Patent, Trademark & Copyright Research Inst., 1966-1970 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Law Center: Patent, Trademark & Copyright Research Inst., 1950-1965 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Librarian: General, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Librarian: General, 1961-1968 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Librarian: Library Advisory Council, 1967-1971 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Pharmacy, School of: Correspondence re Termination of School, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Pharmacy, School of: General, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Registrar's Office: General, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Registrar's Office: General, 1962-1971 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Registrar's Office: Report of, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Registrar's Office: Report of, 1967-1968 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Registrar's Office: Report of, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Registrar's Office: Report of, 1965-1966 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Registrar's Office: Report of, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Registrar's Office: Registration Statistics, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Registrar's Office: Student Body Descriptive Materials, 01/1964 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Special Students, Division of: Abolishment of, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Summer Sessions: General, 1967-1970 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Summer Sessions: General, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - University Students, Division of: General, 1967-1971 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: General, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Personnel, 1967-1972 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Security, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - General, 1966-1972 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research, Dean for - General, 1957-1965 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research, Dean for - FLAC II Computer, 1959-1961 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - HumRRO - General, 10/1969 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - HumRRO - General, 1960-1969 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - HumRRO Contract, Extensions, etc.- Armed Services Board of Contract Appeal, 1958-1961 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - HumRRO Advisory Council, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - Languages of the World Project, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Administration & Research, Vice President of: Sponsored Research - Logistics, 1958-1962 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Development, Vice President for: General, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Development, Vice President for: General, 1966-1970 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Development, Vice President for: (Resources - General), 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Development, Vice President for: (P1ans and Resources), 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Development, Vice President for: John Anthony Brown, Jr., undated (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Development, Vice President for: Ten Year Needs, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Alumni: General, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Alumni: General, 1966-1970 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Alumni: General, 1960-1965 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Alumni: Achievement Awards Procedure, 1964-1966 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Alumni: The Colonials, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Alumni: Annual Support, 1967-1972 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations: General, 1970-1972 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations: General, 1966-1969 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations: General, 1960-1963 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Campaigns: Hospital Building Fund Campaign, 1965-1967 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Campaigns: Law Library Campaign, 1964-1971 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Campaigns: Library Building Campaign, 1965-1970 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Campaigns: Medical Center Campaign, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Campaigns: Medical Center Campaign, 1966-1967 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Campaigns: Medical Center Gift Acknowledgments, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Campaigns: Medical Center Gift Acknowledgments, 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Campaigns: Medical Center Campaign Steering Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Campaigns: Recreational, Physical Education Building Campaign (Smith Center), 1967-1975 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Campaigns: University Center Campaign, 1969-1971 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: General, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Genera1, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: General, 1960-1970 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Advisory Council on Medical Affairs, 1965-1971 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Building (New), 1967-1974 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Clinical Practice Plan, 1964-1969 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Clinica1 Practice Plan, 1959-1966 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Health Plan (GWUHP), 1970-1972 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Medical Affairs, Vice President for - Medical Center: Health Maintenance Organization (HNO), 1971 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Hospital: General, 1965-1971 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Hospital: General, 1959-1965 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Hospital: Joint Construction Grant, Application for, 06/1967 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Hospital: New Addition - Fund Raising Campaign, 1962-1964 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Hospital: New Addition - Fund Raising Thank you letters, 1962-1966 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Hospital: New Addition - Meyer Pavilion, 1960-1965 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Hospital: New Addition - Senate and House Bills - S-2571-HR-8916, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Medicine, School of: General(Not in Box), 1966-1969 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Medicine, School of: General(Not in Box), 1959-1965 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Medicine, School of: Commonwealth Fund, 1958-1967 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Medicine, School of: Deanship (Not in Box), 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Medicine, School of: Educational Program - Three Year, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Medicine, School of: Long Range Plans, 1960-1966 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Medicine, School of: Medical-Dental Legislation - GWU-GU, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Medicine, School of: Medical-Dental Legislation - GWU-GU, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Medicine, School of: Survey Team Report, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Medicine, School of: Survey Team Report, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Medical Center: Me1lon Trust, 1963-1967 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Medical Center: Shrine Burns Center, 1962-1967 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Medical Center: Washington Home for Foundlings - Warwick Memorial Cancer Clinic, 1960-1970 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Medical Center: Washington Home for Foundlings, Complaint filed by, (Cancer Clinic), 1959-1964 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: General, 07/1975-12/1972 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: General, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: General, 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: General, 1966-1967 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Institute for Educational Leadership, 06/1972-12/1972 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Institute for Educational Leadership, 01/1972-06/1972 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Program of Policy Studies in Science & Technology, 1964-1966 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Shaw Urban Renewal Project, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Washington Institute for Educational Leadership (Ford Foundation), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Washington Institute for Education Leadership (Ford Foundation), 1970 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Policy Studies & Special Projects, Vice President for: Washington Internships in Education, 1966-1970 (Box 68, Folder 5)